<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="https://eml.ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.2.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="https://eml.ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.2.0 https://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.3/eml.xsd"
packageId="e5d7a3ae-22d1-452d-a90e-fe237457123e"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
xml:lang="en">
    <dataset>
        <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 0000210-250515123054153</title>
        <creator>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </creator>
        <metadataProvider>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </metadataProvider>
        <pubDate>
                2025-05-15
        </pubDate>
        <language>ENGLISH</language>
        <abstract>
            A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  "RecordedBy" : [
    "is one of (DAVIDSON, CHRISTOPHER, C. DAVIDSON, Davidson C., Davidson C, CHRISTOPHER DAVIDSON)"
  ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
1 records from Washington State University Marion Ownbey Herbarium - Bryophytes
7 records from College of Idaho Herbarium
1 records from University of British Columbia Herbarium (UBC) - Vascular Plant Collection
4 records from Revision of the Nearctic species of the Lasioglossum (Dialictus) gemmatum species complex (Hymenoptera: Halictidae)
40 records from University of Louisiana at Monroe Herbarium, R. Dale Thomas Collection
1 records from USDA United States National Fungus Collections
5 records from LACM Entomology Collection
1 records from Vanderbilt University Herbarium
4 records from Academy of Natural Sciences of Drexel University
89 records from University of Michigan Herbarium
1 records from CHSC - Ahart Herbarium, CSU Chico - Vascular Plants
1 records from A Distribution and Taxonomic Reference Dataset of Geranium (Geraniaceae) in the New World
1 records from Field Museum of Natural History (Botany) Pteridophyte Collection
40 records from Digitalización y Sistematización de las Colecciones Biológicas Nacionales del Instituto de Biología, UNAM (Plantas vasculares)
254 records from Magnoliophyta del Herbario BAB (Instituto de Recursos Biológicos CIRN-INTA)
5 records from MO herbarium -  Missouri Botanical Garden - Amostras Brasileiras Repatriadas - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
2 records from El Género Phaseolus (Leguminosae, Papilionoideae, Phaseoleae) para México
1 records from Catálogo electrónico de especímenes depositados en el Herbario de la Universidad de Texas en Austin, Fase IV (Tipos)
5 records from International Barcode of Life project (iBOL)
1 records from Andrena cyanura Cockerell, a valid North American species
1 records from W herbarium - Naturhistorisches Museum Wien - Amostras Brasileiras Repatriadas - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
4 records from Wisconsin State Herbarium, Vascular Plants
1 records from CEN - Herbário da Embrapa Recursos Genéticos e Biotecnologia
1 records from UF Florida Museum of Natural History Ornithology
8892 records from Tropicos MO Specimen Data
1 records from Arizona State University Lichen Herbarium
1 records from CEPEC - Herbário do Centro de Pesquisas do Cacau
55 records from Computarización del Herbario ENCB, IPN. Fase IV. Base de datos de la familia Pinaceae y de distintas familias de la clase Magnoliopsida depositadas en el Herbario de la Escuela Nacional de Ciencias Biológicas, IPN
105 records from North Carolina State University Vascular Plant Herbarium
133 records from SBBG - Clifton Smith Herbarium, Santa Barbara Botanic Garden
2 records from Estudio taxonómico y base de datos del género Muhlenbergia de México
7 records from RB - Rio de Janeiro Botanical Garden Herbarium Collection
1 records from Árboles mexicanos potencialmente valiosos para la restauración ecológica y la reforestación
4 records from Computarización del Herbario ENCB. Fase II. Base de datos de los ejemplares de la familia Burseraceae y Nyctaginaceae y base de datos digitalizada de los ejemplares tipo de plantas vasculares del Herbario de la Escuela Nacional de Ciencias Biológicas, IPN
1 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Crustacea
1 records from CAS Herpetology (HERP)
9 records from Washington State University Herbarium
1010 records from Snake River Plain Herbarium (Boise State University, Idaho, USA)
529 records from Whitman College Herbarium Vascular Plants
1 records from University of Mississippi, Thomas M. Pullen Herbarium
163 records from Field Museum of Natural History (Botany) Seed Plant Collection
10 records from K herbarium - Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew - Amostras Brasileiras Repatriadas - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
7 records from Miami University Turrell Herbarium - Vascular Plants
128 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Botany
321 records from NY herbarium - The New York Botanical Garden - Amostras Brasileiras Repatriadas - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
35 records from The vascular plants collection (P) at the Herbarium of the Muséum national d'Histoire Naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
7 records from G. S. Torrey Herbarium at the University of Connecticut (CONN)
106 records from HSC - Humboldt State University Vascular Plant Herbarium
1 records from Lund University Biological Museum - Botanical collection (LD)
1 records from Intermountain Herbarium (Vasc. &amp; Algae)
4 records from DAV - University of California, Davis Center for Plant Diversity - Vascular Plants
124 records from Brigham Young University, S. L. Welsh Herbarium
3 records from Herbario Nacional Colombiano (COL)
71 records from CAS Botany (BOT)
223 records from A global database for the distributions of crop wild relatives
2 records from Inventario florístico en Baja California Sur: Región del Cabo e Islas adyacentes
57 records from University of New Mexico Herbarium
6 records from The ‘ red-tailed’ Lasioglossum (Dialictus) (Hymenoptera: Halictidae) of the western Nearctic
307 records from NMNH Extant Specimen Records (USNM, US)
1 records from CEN herbarium -  Embrapa Recursos Genéticos e Biotecnologia - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
3 records from Brigham Young University Arthropod Museum
31 records from Idaho State University, Ray J. Davis Herbarium Vascular Plants
10 records from Harvard University Herbaria: All Records
6 records from Vascular Plant Collection - University of Washington Herbarium (WTU)
9 records from Washington State University Marion Ownbey Herbarium
97 records from Puntos de presencia en Baja California (Botany)
4 records from MEXU/Plantas Vasculares
91 records from The University and Jepson Herbaria -- Lichen
5 records from Herbarium specimens of Université de Montpellier 2, Institut de Botanique (MPU))
81 records from University of Idaho, Stillinger Herbarium Vascular Plants
42 records from UCR - University of California, Riverside Herbarium - Vascular Plants
38 records from Wisconsin State Herbarium, Lichens
9436 records from Tropicos Specimens Non-MO
189 records from The University and Jepson Herbaria -- Vascular Plants
2733 records from RSA - California Botanic Garden Herbarium
2 records from INSDC Sequences
1 records from University of Tennessee Fungal Herbarium
1 records from CSLA - Cal State LA Herbarium
1 records from The genus Begonia (Begoniaceae) in Peru
1 records from University of Tartu Natural History Museum and Botanical Garden Zooloogical Collections
182 records from University of South Florida Herbarium (USF)
227 records from SD - SD Herbarium, San Diego Natural History Museum
18 records from Riqueza y distribución de especies vegetales en la Península de Baja California
6 records from Oregon State University Vascular Plant Collection
709 records from The New York Botanical Garden Herbarium (NY)
8 records from WFVZ Bird Collections
3 records from Desert Botanical Garden Herbarium
9 records from Arizona State University Vascular Plant Herbarium
1 records from University of Tennessee Vascular Herbarium
4 records from Mejoramiento de los modelos de distribución de especies de plantas amenazadas de México (Orchidaceae, Pinaceae, Cupressaceae, Taxaceae, Podocarpaceae) a través de información de sensores remotos y medidas espaciales de incertidumbre en los modelos-conUFZ*

        </abstract>
        <contact>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </contact>

    </dataset>

    <additionalMetadata>
        <metadata>
            <gbif>
                <dateStamp>2025-05-15T14:55:28Z</dateStamp>
                <citation identifier="0000210-250515123054153">GBIF Occurrence Download 0000210-250515123054153</citation>
                <physical>
                    <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                    <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                    <dataFormat>
                        <externallyDefinedFormat>
                            <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                        </externallyDefinedFormat>
                    </dataFormat>
                    <distribution>
                        <online>
                            <url function="download">https://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0000210-250515123054153.zip</url>
                        </online>
                    </distribution>
                </physical>
            </gbif>
        </metadata>
    </additionalMetadata>
    </eml:eml>
